

Pudongxin District, Shanghai, China

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

□ (+86) 131-6701-7220 | ▼77qingliu@gmail.com | 🕏 www.77qingliu.com | 🖸 77QingLiu | 🛅 77qingliu

Summary_

3 years experience specializing in statistical analysis, data mining using SAS/Python/SQL in the pharmaceutical industry. Proficient in data process, data analysis, statistical modeling as well as programming languages such as SAS, Python. Currently working as Statistical Analyst in the Department of Statistics at Eli Lilly China Drug Development and Medical Affairs Center (LCDDMAC), supporting drug development and medical research. Received bachelor degree from Huazhong University of Science and Technology(HUST) with majoring in Public Health in 2015. Parttime Graduate in East China Normal University with majoring in Computer Science. Particularly interested in computer science and data science, especially data mining, data analysis, machine learning, and programming languages such as Python, R, SAS. Strong dedication and pursuit of technology, good self-learning ability, good at learning and studying the latest research results.

Work Experience _____

Eli Lilly & Company Shanghai, China

Nov. 2016 - PRESENT STATISTICAL ANALYST

- · Creating robust programs to import, analyze, interpret and report data from Clinical Trial for regulatory submissions, and manuscripts, as well as for communicating with key colleagues.
- · Organize and analyze data for patterns, trends and strategic insights in supporting medical research and drug development.
- · Assist in selecting statistical methods for data analysis, authoring the corresponding sections of the data analysis plan, and conducting the actual analysis once a reporting database is created.
- Implement open source technology (eg. Python, R) to drive innovation and improve work efficiency, avoid tedious work and save working time.

PAREXEL International Shanghai, China

STATISTICAL PROGRAMMER Jun. 2015 - Dov. 2016

- Building complex and reusable programs to automate the process of Data Cleaning, Validation, Analysis and Report generation.
- Production of well-formatted datasets(SDTM, ADaM) and table, listing, figures using SAS software for Phase I-IV trials and FDA submissions.

Presentation & Publication

PharmaSUG China 2017 Shanghai, China

PRESENTER Jul. 2017

• Streamline Table Lookup by Embedding HASH in FCMP

Neuropsychiatric Disease and Treatment

Worldwide

AUTHOR Jan. 2018

· Reliability and validity of the Chinese version of questionnaire-Children with Difficulties for Chinese Children or Adolescents with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder: a cross-sectional survey

Open Sourced Projects.

SAS-Syntax-and-Theme A SAS syntax highlighting package powered by regex in Sublime Text 3(download up to 4K)

Algorithms Data Structure/Algorithms implemented in Python

AutoGenaCRF A set of SAS macros strove to automatically generate aCRF for FDA submission.

Skills_

Programming SAS, Python(Proficient). R, C(Knowledgeble)

Data Science Statistical Analysis, Statistical Modeling, Data Manipulate, Data Visualization, Machine Learning

Languages English, Chinese

Honors & Awards

LCDDMAC Excellence Award, Eli Lilly & Company

Outstanding Graduate, Huazhong University of Science and Technology

Shanghai, China Wuhan, China

Education

HUST(Huazhong University of Science and Technology)

• Core Curriculum: Health Statistics, Epidemiology, Multivariate Statistics

Wuhan, China

B.S. IN PREVENTIVE MEDICINE

Sep. 2010 - Jun. 2015

77QINGLIU · RÉSUMÉ APRIL 7, 2018